<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="poacher_game_success_text">After a short while you see the poacher %1$s climb over the fence of warehouse with a loaded poach on the shoulder. According to poacher´s observation, there is a truck in the area of warehouse, which - as you all agreed - is bit better way of transport over desert than going by foot. However, you´ve noticed small group of armed forces patrolling around the warehouse. What approach will you choose to get inside?</string>
    <string name="poacher_game_failure_text">After a short while you see the poacher alongside the half-empty poach being thrown out of the main gate of the warehouse. The poacher %1$s limps towards you and reports, that there is a truck in the area of warehouse, which - as you all agreed - is bit better way of transport over desert than going by foot. However, you´ve noticed small group of armed forces patrolling around the warehouse. What approach will you choose to get inside?</string>
    <string name="poacher_game_guns_blazing">It\'s just a small group, we will go in guns blazing!</string>
    <string name="poacher_game_sneaky_sneaky">There can be far more armed guys. Let\'s try to sneak inside…</string>

    <string name="guns_blazing_text">After you start direct attack on the warehouse you find out, that there are much more enemy troops than you expected, and after a short while, you are forced to take cover in a building near gate to the warehouse area. During relatively friendly exchange of bullets and grenades you find the mechanism for opening the gate of area. However, it cannot be operated without a special access card, which is kinda pitiful, because driving through closed gate is quite unpleasant hobby. Unless! Unless you have someone in your team, who can handle difficult circuits and captious ports.</string>

    <string name="sneaky_sneaky_text">You successfully approach the warehouse area, cut the fence and go inside. However, you are immediately forced to hide in nearest building near the gate to the area, because you were most likely spotted by passing patrol. In following seconds, you calm your breath and think, what to do with approaching patrol.</string>
    <string name="sneaky_sneaky_come_inside">Let them come inside the building and then try to eliminate them - risk direct fight</string>
    <string name="sneaky_sneaky_shoot_asap">Wait until they get to range and then shoot both of them - risk raising the alarm</string>

    <string name="come_inside_text">With tension equal to one of suspenders being tensed over half-meter belly you await coming of the patrol. As soon as the door opens, you silently eliminate both patrolling soldiers. Although you haven\'t raised the alarm yet, the others will surely start to miss the patrol shortly. During more thorough exploration of the building you are in, you find the mechanism for opening the gate of area. However, it cannot be operated without a special access card, which is kinda pitiful, because driving through closed gate is quite unpleasant hobby. Unless! Unless you have someone in your team, who can handle difficult circuits and captious ports.</string>

    <string name="shoot_asap_text">Hidden behind rack with tools you unlock your guns and once the heads of patrolling troops appear in your sights, you fire. The answer to your actions is deafening sound of alarm followed by shower of bullets raining upon the sheet metal lining of the building you are in. During relatively friendly exchange of bullets and grenades you find the mechanism for opening the gate of area. However, it cannot be operated without a special access card, which is kinda pitiful, because driving through closed gate is quite unpleasant hobby. Unless! Unless you have someone in your team, who can handle difficult circuits and captious ports.</string>

    <string name="porter_call_out">This is a child\'s play for the porter %1$s</string>
</resources>